Advertisement

Toggle navigation

[Home](https://www.thetvdb.com/) /

Whip Networks, Inc. - TheTVDB Privacy Policy
============================================

Updated and Effective Date: This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is effective and was last updated as of January 3, 2024.

This Privacy Policy applies to Whip Networks, Inc.'s ("WNI") services offered via the TheTVDB.com website (the "**Site**") and describes our practices with regard to the data we collect in connection with the Site for both business users and consumers. If the individual accessing or using the Site ("You") is doing so as the authorized user of a company to which we are providing services under a contract, Your use may be subject to the terms of that contract.

**Table of Contents**

1. [The Information We Collect](#section1)
2. [How We Use Your Information](#section2)
3. [How We Share Your Information](#section3)
4. [Third Party Advertising and Analytics Providers](#section4)
5. [Third Party Content and Links](#section5)
6. [Your Choices About the Information We Collect](#section6)
7. [Security of Your Information](#section7)
8. [General Audience Site](#section8)
9. [Changes to This Privacy Policy](#section9)
10. [Consent to International Transfer of Your Information](#section10)
11. [How Long We Retain Your Information](#section11)
12. [Contact Us](#section12)
13. [Notice to Nevada Residents](#section13)
14. [Additional Information for European Union, European Economic Area, and United Kingdom Residents](#section14)
15. [Additional Information for Canadian Residents](#section15)
16. [Notice to California Residents](#section16)

1. ### The Information We Collect
    
    The Site collects information from You when You use it. Some of this information may be considered "personal information" under various applicable laws. We consider information that identifies You as a specific, identified individual to be personal information (such as Your name and email address), and we treat additional information, including IP addresses and cookie identifiers, as "personal information" where required by applicable law. Note that we may de-identify personal information so that it is non-personal, such as by aggregating it or converting it to a code ("hash"). We maintain and use de-identified data without attempting to re-identify it, except where permitted by applicable law, such as to determine whether our de-identification process satisfies legal requirements. We will treat de-identified information as non-personal to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law. 
    
    We collect information when You visit or interact with the Site, including:
    
    **Information You Submit.** The information You submit to us will depend on how You engage with us. For instance, if You create an account with us, You will need to provide Your contact information (Your name and email address) and a password; if you are using the Site to share information publicly such as your custom lists, or to identify your favorite series or movies, you will need to provide information about those preferences and interests and if You are subscribing to receive the TVDB API, You will need to provide payment information. You may also upload entertainment related and other content to the Site, and we may ask for additional information either through the Site or through surveys, such as demographic data, Your experience with the Site, or information about Your opinions, interests and preferences.
    
    **Information We Collect Automatically.** The Site collects certain information whenever You visit it or otherwise interact with it ("Usage Information"). Usage Information may include the hardware model, browser, and operating system You are using, the URL or advertisement that referred You to the webpage You are visiting, all of the areas within the Site that You visit, Your time zone, and mobile network (if applicable), among other information. In addition, we automatically collect Your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for any computer, mobile phone or other device You use to access our Site. We may be able to collect or infer Your approximate location based on Your IP address or similar information we collect. As You use the Site, we may also track how You interact with our content.
    
    The methods that may be used to collect Usage Information include the following:
    
    **Cookies and Local Storage** small text files stored locally on Your device that help store user preferences. These technologies are able to store a unique identifier for a device to us to recognize the device whenever the device is used to visit the Site. These technologies may be used for many purposes by us, our service providers, and our third-party business partners, such as automatically collecting Usage Information, enabling features, serving advertisements to You on our Site, and remembering Your preferences. We may use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on the Site, to study the effectiveness of our customer communications, and to personalize Your experience through the Site, such as to recognize You when You return to them. The information we store includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. If You do not want to accept cookies, You can block them by adjusting the settings on Your Internet browser. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
    
    **Web beacons (also known as clear GIFs and pixel tags)** are small pieces of code used to collect usage analytics. They help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or not and, if so, how many times. When You ask us to send You information or a promotion or a newsletter, we will use web beacons to establish how many of the emails are actually opened. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon.
    
    We use similar tools to collect such information from mobile devices. In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes.
    
    **Social Media Platforms**. TheTVDB.com permits You to interact with social media platforms, including Facebook and Twitter. When You interact with third party platforms through the Site, we will receive information about You. We may also receive information about You if other users of social media give us access to their profiles and You are one of their connections or "friends." The information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party's privacy practices, including, without limitation, whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and Your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party website or service. We or the third party may allow You to disable or remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about You through the application or feature, but we may retain the information previously collected.
    
    If You choose to post information to a third party platform, that information may be public and the third party may have access to information about You and Your use of the Site. You may also choose to participate in a way that connects that third-party service with our Site, such as posting to one of our pages on a social media site. Doing so may allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about You, including personal information, and the third party may allow us to re-post content related to us on our own services.
    
    In addition, these third parties may set their own cookies and collect information about Your use of TheTVDB.com, including Your IP address or other device identifiers, and which pages You visit on our Site. Certain third party platforms may be able to collect certain information on Your visits to TheTVDB.com regardless of whether or not You affirmatively interact with the feature and whether or not You are logged into (or have) an account.
    
2. ### How We Use Your Information
    
    We may use non-personal information for any purpose. We also use information that we collect, including personal information and Usage Information, to: (1) provide the services You request and allow You to participate in features we offer, or to provide related customer service; (2) to process Your subscription order; (3) to tailor content, recommendations, and offers we display to You on TheTVDB.com; (4) recognize You across our Site; (5) process Your requests, questions, or feedback, including to provide You with technical support; (6) provide You with information, products, or services that You have requested or that we think may interest You; (7) investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies, which may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts, or other government entities; (8) process Your registration, including verifying Your information is active and valid; (9) improve the Site and for internal business purposes; (10) contact You with regard to Your use of the Site and, in our discretion, changes to the Site's policies; and (11) for purposes disclosed at the time You provide Your personal information or otherwise with Your consent.
    
3. ### How We Share Your Information
    
    We may share non-personal information, such as aggregated statistics or de-identified data, for any purpose in our discretion. We do not share Your personal information with third parties for those third parties' own direct marketing purposes unless we provide You the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out prior to such sharing. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about You, including personal information and Usage Information, as disclosed at the time You provide us with Your information or with Your consent, and as described in this Privacy Policy, including as set forth below.
    
    1. **Publicly Posted Content/At Your Request.** We will share Your information if You request or consent to that sharing, including whenever You share via social media or You post publicly on the Site, such as by creating a list. Please note that certain information, such as Your user name, may be publicly displayed on the Site along with the publicly posted content.
    2. **Service Providers.** We contract with certain companies to perform services on our behalf, including advertising, marketing assistance, e-mail delivery, hosting services, site maintenance and repair, security, quality assurance, customer service, surveys, and data research and analysis, and provide Your information to them in furtherance of such services.
    3. **In Connection With Business Transitions.** In the event WNI undergoes a business transition, such as a merger with or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer Your personal information and other information to the successor organization in connection with such transaction, including during the course of any due diligence. By providing Your personal information, You agree that we may transfer such information to the other entity in such a transaction without Your further consent.
    4. **For Administrative and Legal Reasons.** We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation, or legal request; to protect the integrity of the Site; to fulfill Your requests; to cooperate in a law enforcement investigation, an investigation on a public safety matter, or an investigation into claims of intellectual property infringement; to protect and defend the legal rights and/or property of WNI and any of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and shareholders, or the Site, any of their users, or any other party; or, in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of users or the general public.
4. ### Third Party Advertising and Analytics Providers
    
    WNI works with third party business partners such as online advertising companies, analytics providers, and other partners to serve our ads online, to serve third party ads through the Site and to provide us with information regarding the use of the Site and the effectiveness of our advertisements. We allow these companies to place tracking technologies like cookies and web tags on the Site, and they may otherwise collect or have access to Usage Information and other information about You. Some of these parties may collect personal information over time when You visit the Site or other online websites and services. We may share information, typically information that has been aggregated or de-identified, Usage Information, and location information with third party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other third parties including for targeted advertising purposes.
    
    Some of the third parties we use to perform advertising and analytics services may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA"). You may wish to visit [optout.networkadvertising.org](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the opt-out procedures of NAI members, including opt out mechanisms for web browsers, mobile and other connected devices, and a tool to opt out from participating NAI members using Your hashed email address for interest-based advertising. You may also want to visit [optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an opt-out for DAA-participating companies. If You are a California resident, please see our ["Notice to California Residents" section below](https://thetvdb.com/privacy-policy#section17) regarding additional rights You have, including how to exercise Your "Do Not Sell" right.
    
    We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about the use of the Site and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information about the use of other websites, apps, and online services. You can learn about Google's practices by going to [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
    
    This website uses Adnimation to manage its programmatic ad sales, which may include the use of first and third-party cookies to collect non-sensitive, anonymized data for ad targeting purposes. Users can opt-out of personalized advertising by adjusting browser settings. You can review Adnimation's cookie and privacy policy [here.](https://www.adnimation.com/privacy-policy/)
    
    If You are a California resident, please see our [Notice to California Residents](https://thetvdb.com/privacy-policy#section17) regarding additional rights You have, including how to exercise Your "Do Not Sell or Share" right.
    
5. ### Third Party Content and Links
    
    The Site may contain links to third party websites, services, applications, or content that You elect to access through our Site. When You navigate away from the Site to such third party sites or content, this Privacy Policy does not apply, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party.
    
6. ### Your Choices About the Information We Collect
    
    You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information You submit to us, such as Your contact information associated with Your account. If You have an account, You will have a profile section within Your account that allows You to update certain personal information You have provided. You may also contact us at legal@whipmedia.com if You have questions about or wish to modify certain information that we have collected from or about You. In addition, when You modify Your personal information or change Your preferences, information that You remove may persist internally for our administrative purposes or within backup media.
    
    If we send You marketing email communications, You will have the ability to opt-out using the mechanism provided in the emails. Please note that we reserve the right to send You certain non-marketing communications relating to Your account or use of the Site, such as administrative and services announcements and other transactional emails.
    
    If You are a resident of certain jurisdictions, you may have additional rights. Please see our Jurisdiction Specific Notices for more information.
    
7. ### Security of Your Information
    
    We implement commercially reasonable measures to protect the security of Your information. However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge You to take steps to keep Your personal information (including Your account password) safe and to log out of Your account after use.
    
8. ### General Audience Site
    
    The Site is not intended for children Younger than the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children Younger than the age of 16.
    
9. ### Changes to this Privacy Policy
    
    It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations and industry standards. Accordingly, to the extent allowed by applicable law, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will inform You by posting a notice on the Site. We may also provide notice to You in other ways, such as through contact information You have provided. Your continued use of the Site after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy will constitute Your consent to those changes to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law.
    
10. ### Consent to International Transfer of Your Information
    
    We are a US-based company. If You are located outside of the United States, please be aware that the information that we collect from You will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of Your country. By using the Site or providing us with any information, You fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing, and storage of Your information in the United States and other jurisdictions, which may have different or less protective privacy laws than those in Your country. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States and other countries according to the laws in those jurisdictions. Your information will also be disclosed to third parties as described in the “How We Share Your Information” section above.
    
11. ### How Long We Retain Your Information
    
    We retain Your Personal Data while You have an account with us and while You continue to use or visit the Site. We will retain Your Personal Data for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the Site to You; exercise the choices and rights You have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; enforce our terms for use of the Site; and comply with legal and regulatory requirements.
    
12. ### Contact Us
    
    If You have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and/or our practices, please contact us at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404, or at legal@whipmedia.com. When writing to us, please specify that You are writing about The TVDB’s Privacy Policy and practices.

JURISDICTION SPECIFIC RIGHTS
----------------------------

13. ### Notice to Nevada Residents
    
    Nevada S.B. 220 provides Nevada residents who are using the Site for personal, family, or household purposes with the ability to opt out of the sale of their personal information. We do not sell Your personal information as defined in S.B. 220. However, You may still submit an opt-out request, and if our practices were to change in the future, we would honor Your request. If You are a Nevada resident and would like to opt out of the sale of Your covered information, Your request must be submitted to legal@whipmedia.com. Your request must include Your full name, street address, city, state, zip code, and a valid email address so that we can contact You if needed regarding Your request. If You previously provided a phone number, including it will assist us in making sure we identify You as someone who wants to opt out. You may be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time to verify Your identity and/or the authenticity of Your request.
    
14. ### Additional Information for European Union, European Economic Area, and United Kingdom Residents
    
    #### EU/EEA/UK Data Subject Rights
    
    The GDPR (EU General Data Protection Regulation) provides certain rights for EU/EEA residents. Residents of the United Kingdom have similar rights under the Data Privacy Act. You can access information about You and update or correct it. In some cases, You can also ask us to erase it, restrict or stop processing, or provide data in a "portable" form, if feasible. You may withdraw consent ("opt-out") if You have previously consented to any particular use of Your information, such as receiving emails or text messages. For all requests, contact legal@whipmedia.com. You may also decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide some or all of the features and functionality of our Site.
    
    You may make changes to the Personal Data collected by our account registration pages as described in the **"Your Choices About the Information We Collect"** section, above. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide You reasonable access to Your Personal Data within 30 days of Your access request to the contact address below. We provide this access so that You may review, make corrections, or request deletion of Your Personal Data. If we cannot honor Your request within 30 days, we will inform You when we will be able to provide such access. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation as to why access is denied. When technically feasible, at Your request, we will provide Your Personal Data to You or transmit it directly to another controller.
    
    **Inquiries and Complaints**
    
    Please first contact us as set forth below. EU/EEA and UK residents have the right to make a complaint to Your national data protection supervisory authority if You do not believe we have resolved Your concern.
    
    **Contact Us**
    
    For all EU/EEA and UK Data Subject Rights requests, please put the statement "Your EU/EEA/UK Data Subject Rights" in the subject field of Your request. Please provide Your contact information in Your request and clearly indicate that You are requesting information with respect to the TVDB Site.
    
    Email: legal@whipmedia.com
    
    Address: 132a Webber Street, Southwark, London SE1 0QL
    
15. ### Additional Information for Canadian Residents
    
    We make reasonable efforts to notify You of the purposes for which personal information will be used or disclosed and if the initial purpose changes. Please note, You may withdraw consent at any time (subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice). Subject to certain limits set out in the applicable laws, Canadian residents also have the right to request access to the personal information that WNI collects and to update or correct personal information if it is inaccurate.
    
    If You are a Canadian resident and would like to submit a request to access Your personal information or to withdraw consent to the processing of Your personal data, You must submit Your request by sending an email to legal@whipmedia.com. You may also use this contact to submit any requests for information on WNI’s privacy practices or to submit a complaint regarding our practices.
    
    Your request or complaint must include Your full name, street address, city, province, postal code, and an email address so that we are able to contact You if needed regarding this request.
    
    We cannot properly process requests or complaints that do not come through the designated request mechanism or do not contain sufficient information to allow us to process Your request. You may also be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time in order to verify Your identity and/or the authenticity of the request. Once Your request is processed, absent exemptions, we will provide You with details regarding what personal information we have, how it is used, and with which third parties it is shared.
    
    Canadian residents may have additional rights under Canadian law, including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and successor legislation. Please see the website of the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada (www.priv.gc.ca) for further information.
    
    Canadian residents also may learn more about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties in Canada at the Canadian DAA choice page at [https://Youradchoices.ca/choices](https://youradchoices.ca/choices).
    
    You and we confirm that it is our wish that this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Service, and all other related policies be drawn up in English. _Vous reconnaissent avoir exigé la rédaction en anglais du présent document ainsi que tous les documents qui s'y rattachent._
    
16. ### Notice to California Residents
    
    **This California Privacy Notice is effective as of January 3, 2024.**
    
    This notice supplements the TVDB Privacy Policy. Terms (including defined capitalized terms) used in this California Privacy Notice have the same meanings given in the California Consumer Privacy Act, the California Privacy Rights Act of 2023, and any implementing regulations adopted thereunder (collectively, the "CCPA"), unless otherwise defined.
    
    * **Exercising Your Rights**
        
        The CCPA provides California users with the right to request (1) that we disclose to You what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to You the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about You ("**Right to Know**"); and (2) that we delete the Personal Information we collected about You ("**Right to Delete**"), (3) that we correct inaccurate Personal Information we hold about you ("**Right** **to** **Correct**"), (4) to opt-out from the sharing of your Personal Information to a third party for cross-context behavioral advertising (i.e., targeted advertising) ("**Right to Opt-Out of Sharing**"), (5) to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information ("**Right to Opt-Out of Sale**"), and (6) that we limit the use or disclosure of your Sensitive Personal Information (SPI) to purposes set forth under the CCPA, including what is necessary and anticipated to perform the services or provide the goods reasonably expected by an average consumer who requests those goods or services ("**Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of SPI**"), all subject to meanings and exceptions set forth in the CCPA. More information on how to exercise these rights is below.
        
        Please note that our business activities do not use personal information in a manner that triggers the Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of SPI.
        
        California users have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights. We will not discriminate against You for exercising Your CCPA rights.
        
    * **Verifying Requests**
        
        Please note that we will take reasonable steps to verify Your identity in order to fulfill Your request. In addition to Your user name and email address, we may ask for additional information, such as Your transactions with us (e.g., a series or movie You have marked as a favorite).
        
        In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to process the request. When you exercise your Right to Know, Right to Delete, and/or Right to Correct, we may ask that you provide us with information, beyond the above, in order to verify your identity and fulfill your request.
        
    * **Agents**
        
        If You are an authorized representative submitting a request on a user's behalf, please submit the request per the instructions below We will follow up to request a signed, written permission signed by the individual who is the subject of the request authorizing You to make the request on their behalf. The written permission must state Your full legal name, the full legal name of the individual who is the subject of the request and needs to be clear about the permission granted.
        
        Alternatively, You may submit a copy of a power of attorney under Probate Code sections 4000-4465. In either case, please also indicate in Your email the nature of Your request. The consumer's identity, in addition to Your own, will need to be independently verified in order for us to be able to fulfill Your request. We may also ask the consumer to directly confirm with us that they provided You permission to submit a request. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that You are authorized to act on the consumer's behalf, we may deny the request. If You have questions about any of these rights, please contact us at [legal@whipmedia.com](mailto:legal@whipmedia.com).
        
    * **Submitting Your Requests**
        
        If You are a California Consumer and would like to exercise your rights please email us at legal@whipmedia.com or mail us Your request at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404. Your request must include Your user name (if you have one) and email address; please also include any additional information that You have submitted to us that may help us verify You as set forth below.
        
    * **Other Important Information**
        
        Requests to Know: In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we will require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that You are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
        
        Requests to Delete: To ensure that we do not delete Your personal information in response to a fraudulent request, once You submit the request, we may follow up to confirm that You want Your information to be deleted.
        
        Do Not Sell or Share for Cross-Context Behavioral Advertising: As required under CCPA, WNI provides a right to California users of the Site to request to opt-out of the sale and sharing of Personal Information (i.e., for targeted advertising). WNI does not sell personal information for monetary compensation, but as described above, certain third-party advertising partners and analytics companies may collect data from visitors to the Site, and these may be considered "sales" or "sharing" under the CCPA. Click here (Cookies Settings) to manage your cookie preferences for the Site. In addition, the Digital Advertising Alliance also offers tools for California consumers to send requests under the CCPA to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of the participating companies. See: https://www.privacyrights.info/.
        
        Note that these are cookie-based opt-outs, so if You disable Your cookies or upgrade Your browser after opting out, or if You use different computers or browsers, You will need to indicate Your opt-out choices across those other computers and browsers.
        
    * **Do Not Track**
        
        Some browsers incorporate a 'Do Not Track' (DNT) feature that, when turned on, signals to websites and online services that you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet an accepted standard for how to respond to browser DNT signals, we do not currently respond to them.
        
    * **Users Younger than Age 16**
        
        WNI does not knowingly sell Personal Information of minors younger than 16 years of age.
        
    * **Data Retention**
        
        We retain your Personal Information while you have an account with us and while you continue to use or visit the Site. We will retain your Personal Information for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this California Notice, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the Site to you; exercise the choices and rights you have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; enforce our terms for use; and comply with legal and regulatory requirements, including if a longer retention period is permitted or required by law.
        
    * **Personal Information WNI Collects**
        
        We collect certain types of information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device ("Personal Information"). The Personal Information we collect about You will depend on how You use the Site or otherwise interact with us. Accordingly, we may not collect all of the below information about You.
        
        _In addition to the below, we may collect and/or use additional types of information, and will do so after providing notice to You and obtaining Your consent to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA._
        
        |     |     |     |     |     |
        | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
        | **Category of Personal Information Collected** | **Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected** | **Categories of Sources from Which Collected** | **Categories of Third Parties with whom Information is Shared/Disclosed for Business Purpose** | **Categories of Third Parties to Whom This Type of Personal Information Is Sold or Shared** |
        | A. Identifiers<br><br>Examples: name, user name, email address, and device identifiers | To provide the Site to You and allow You to participate in the features the Site offer<br><br>To help us to improve the Site and to serve You better<br><br>To send you communications<br><br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes<br><br>To protect against misuse of the Site, fraud, or criminal activity<br><br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Site<br><br>For other purposes described to You at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You<br><br>Third party service providers and business partners<br><br>Cookies and other tracking technologies | Other Users<br><br>Service Providers<br><br>Third parties whose features are integrated with the Site, such as social media companies<br><br>Third party advertising and analytics companies<br><br>Third parties who may acquire Your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition<br><br>Third parties or affiliated companies when You request that we share Your information with them<br><br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party<br><br>Third parties when You agree to or request that we share Your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar marketing partners may have access to this data, including in order to better service you relevant advertisements, and this may be considered a "sale" or "share" under the CCPA in certain circumstances. |
        | B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))<br><br>Examples: name, email address, phone number | To provide the Site to You and allow You to participate in the features the Site offer<br><br>To help us to improve the Site and to serve You better<br><br>To send you communications<br><br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes<br><br>To protect against misuse of the Site, fraud, or criminal activity<br><br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Site<br><br>For other purposes described to You at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You<br><br>Other Users<br><br>Third party service providers and business partners<br><br>Cookies and other tracking technologies | Other Users<br><br>Service Providers<br><br>Third parties whose features are integrated with the Site, such as social media companies<br><br>Third party advertising and analytics companies<br><br>Third parties who may acquire Your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition<br><br>Third parties or affiliated companies when You request that we share Your information with them<br><br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party<br><br>Third parties when You agree to or request that we share Your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar marketing partners may have access to this data, including in order to better service you relevant advertisements, and this may be considered a "sale" or "share" under the CCPA in certain circumstances. |
        | C. Commercial information<br><br>Examples: products or services obtained or considered; purchasing or consuming history or tendency | To provide the Site to You and allow You to participate in the features the Site offer<br><br>To help us improve the Site and to serve You better<br><br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes<br><br>To protect against misuse of the Site, fraud, or criminal activity<br><br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Site<br><br>For other purposes described to You at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You<br><br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users<br><br>Service Providers<br><br>Third parties whose features are integrated with the Site, such as social media companies<br><br>Third party advertising and analytics companies<br><br>Third parties who may acquire Your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition<br><br>Third parties or affiliated companies when You request that we share Your information with them<br><br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party<br><br>Third parties when You agree to or request that we share Your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar marketing partners may have access to this data, including in order to better service you relevant advertisements, and this may be considered a "sale" or "share" under the CCPA in certain circumstances. |
        | D. Internet or other similar network activity<br><br>Examples: login information, areas of the Site You visit, and devices used to access the Site | To provide the Site to You and allow You to participate in the features the Site offer<br><br>To communicate with you<br><br>To help us improve the Site and to serve You better<br><br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes<br><br>To protect against misuse of the Site, fraud, or criminal activity<br><br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Site<br><br>For other purposes described to You at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | Cookies and other tracking technologies<br><br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users<br><br>Service Providers<br><br>Third parties whose features are integrated with the Site, such as social media companies<br><br>Third party advertising and analytics companies<br><br>Third parties who may acquire Your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition<br><br>Third parties or affiliated companies when You request that we share Your information with them<br><br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party<br><br>Third parties when You agree to or request that we share Your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar marketing partners may have access to this data, including in order to better service you relevant advertisements, and this may be considered a "sale" or "share" under the CCPA in certain circumstances. |
        | E. Inferences drawn from other personal information<br><br>Examples: Preferences, characteristics, predispositions, behaviors | To provide the Site to You and allow You to participate in the features the Site offer<br><br>To help us improve the Site and to serve You better<br><br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes<br><br>To protect against misuse of the Site, fraud, or criminal activity<br><br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Site<br><br>For other purposes described to You at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You<br><br>Third party service providers<br><br>Cookies and tracking technologies<br><br>Third party social media companies<br><br>Third party business partners such as data analytics providers, data brokers, advertising networks, or joint marketing partners | Other Users<br><br>Service Providers<br><br>Third parties whose features are integrated with the Site, such as social media companies<br><br>Third party advertising and analytics companies<br><br>Third parties who may acquire Your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition<br><br>Third parties or affiliated companies when You request that we share Your information with them<br><br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party<br><br>Third parties when You agree to or request that we share Your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar marketing partners may have access to this data, including in order to better service you relevant advertisements, and this may be considered a "sale" or "share" under the CCPA in certain circumstances. |
        
    * **Other California Rights for Non-Business Users**
        
        California residents who provide companies conducting business in California with information primarily for personal, family, or household purposes, have the right to request certain information relating to third parties to which the company has disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as WNI does, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. WNI will provide You choice prior to sharing Your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If You do not opt-in or if You choose to opt-out at the time WNI offers that choice, we will not share Your personal information with that third party for its direct marketing purposes.
        
        California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing legal@whipmedia.com or writing to us at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404. You must put the statement "Your TVDB California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of Your email or in the address line of Your envelope. You must include Your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

##### About

##### Discover

##### Legal

##### Follow Us

[](https://www.thetvdb.com/) © 2024 TheTVDB.com ®, A Whip Media Company. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
